School of Engineering and Applied Science Records, 1884-2017: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 1: Dean of the School of Engineering and Applied Science, 1896-2016 September 13; 149.37 linear feet 121 boxes Digital Folders: 97, Digital Files: 2,135 73,438 email messages
  - Subseries 1E: H. Vincent Poor, 2004 November 30-2016 September 13; AR.2016.046; Digital Folders: 97, Digital Files: 2,135 73,438 email messages
    - Desktop Files, 2004 November 30-2016 June 21; Digital Folders: 84, Digital Files: 2,102
      - Strategic Plan, 2012 January 12 - 2016 February 11; Digital Folders: 1, Digital Files: 11
      - Testimonial sheets, 2014 April 09 - 2014 April 09; Digital Folders: 1, Digital Files: 6
      - Trustees Reports, 2012 January 06 - 2016 March 08; Digital Folders: 14, Digital Files: 95
      - Turing, 2011 May 24 - 2011 May 24; Digital Folders: 1, Digital Files: 2
      - Uncategorized Files, 2006 April 25 - 2016 June 21; Digital Folders: 1, Digital Files: 881
    - Email Correspondence, 2005 October 11-2016 September 13; Digital Folders: 12, Digital Files: 33 73,438 email messages
      The emails within this group of records document electronic communications Dean Poor conducted primarily with staff within the School of Engineering and Applied Science, faculty members at Princeton, and University administrators. Topics covered include the school’s various research programs, financial well-being, and general administrative matters. The file with the largest volume of messages (17,511 messages) is Development, in which the most frequent correspondent is Jane R. Maggard, Associate Dean for Development at the School. The second most voluminous file is Faculty (13,057 messages), which contains significant correspondence with Lynn Loo, engineering professor and Director of the Andlinger Center.
      This group of records retains its original arrangement as when transferred to the University Archives.
      - Admin, 2006 April 04 - 2016 June 22; 10,910 messages Digital Folders: 1, Digital Files: 3
      - CIEE (Center for Innovation in Engineering Education), 2005 October 11 - 2016 June 21; 2,923 messages Digital Folders: 1, Digital Files: 3
      - Communications, 2006 June 07 - 2016 June 21; 5,401 messages Digital Folders: 1, Digital Files: 3
      - Development, 2006 January 04 - 2016 September 13; 17,511 messages Digital Folders: 1, Digital Files: 3
      - Events, 2008 September 21 - 2016 June 17; 2,948 messages Digital Folders: 1, Digital Files: 3
      - Facilities, 2006 April 24 - 2016 June 20; 4,200 messages Digital Folders: 1, Digital Files: 3
      - Faculty, 2006 March 31 - 2016 August 16; 13,057 messages Digital Folders: 1, Digital Files: 3
      - Financial, 2006 May 05 - 2016 June 23; 2,104 messages Digital Folders: 1, Digital Files: 3
      - Research, 2006 April 11 - 2016 August 14; 9,741 messages Digital Folders: 1, Digital Files: 3
      - Students, 2007 October 09 - 2016 June 22; 4,172 messages Digital Folders: 1, Digital Files: 3
      - Visitors, 2008 March 07 - 2016 May 03; 471 messages Digital Folders: 1, Digital Files: 3
- Series 2: Students and Alumni, 1884-1979; 5.42 linear feet 5 boxes
  Restricted for 75 years from the date of the creation of the record.
  The Students and Alumni series documents the relationship between the School of Engineering and Applied science, its students, and its alumni. Contained in the series are questionnaires sent to alumni of the early engineering departments, the academic record cards of students, as well as the records of the Princeton Engineering Association, the School's main alumni organization.
  Arranged by subject.
  - Student Academic Record Cards, 1938-1979; 3 boxes
    - Class of, 1938; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 1)
      [restricted for 75 years]
    - Class of, 1939; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Class of, 1940; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Class of, 1942; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Class of, 1943; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Class of, 1944; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Class of, 1945; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Class of, 1946; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Class of, 1947; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Class of, 1949; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Graduate School, 1960-1969; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Class of, 1950; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Class of, 1951; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Class of, 1952; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Class of, 1953; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Class of, 1954; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Class of, 1955; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Class of, 1956; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Class of, 1957; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Class of, 1958; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Class of, 1959; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Class of, 1960; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Class of, 1961; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Class of, 1962; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Class of, 1963; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Class of, 1964; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Class of, 1965; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Class of, 1966; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Class of, 1967; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - Class of, 1968; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - Class of, 1969; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 20)
    - Class of, 1970; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Class of, 1971; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Class of, 1972; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Class of, 1974; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Class of, 1975; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Class of, 1976; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Class of, 1977; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Class of, 1978; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Class of, 1979; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Questionnaires, 1884-1924; 10 folders
    - Class of, 1884; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Class of, 1889; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Class of, 1894; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Class of, 1899; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Class of, 1904; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Class of, 1909; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Class of, 1914; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Class of, 1922; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Class of, 1923; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Class of, 1924; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Princeton Engineering Society, 1928-1942; 3 folders
    - Correspondence, 1932-1935; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Papers, 1928-1942; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Prize Essay Contest, 1936; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Princeton Engineering Association, 1916-1971; 18 folders
    - Minutes of Meetings and Announcements, 1921-1971; 9 folders
      - 1921-1923, 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 4)
      - 1924-1928, 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 5)
      - 1929-1938, 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 6)
      - 1939-1948, 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 7)
      - 1949-1952, 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 8)
      - 1953-1957, 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 9)
      - 1958-1961, 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 10)
      - 1962-1966, 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 11)
      - 1967-1971, 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Chronological File of Correspondence, 1921-1937; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - Chronological File of Correspondence, 1939-1970; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - Committee on Education, 1931-1944; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - Exchange Student Program, 1951-1952; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - Form Letters and Notices, 1932-1947; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 17)
    - Membership Directories, 1928-1957; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 18)
    - Historical Miscellany, 1916-1957; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 19)
    - The Princeton Engineer, 1948-1970; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 20)
    - Secretary's and Treasurer's Reports, 1939-1943; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 21)
    - Princeton Engineering Association, undated; 1 item
- Series 3: Departments and Centers, 1834-2002 August; 36.36 linear feet 35 boxes
  The Departments and Centers series consists of the records of the various departments (and in later years, research centers) which fall under the authority of the School of Engineering. As engineering has progressed rapidly over the course of the 20th century, many of these departments have undergone changes in title, mergers, or been disbanded completely. For the purposes of description, the names used here reflect the name of the Department or Center at the date of the most recent records found in the corresponding subseries.
  The Departments and Centers series is divided into five subseries.
  - Subseries 3A: Department of Chemical Engineering, 1929-1962; 7.5 linear feet 6 boxes
    The Department of Chemical Engineering subseries contains the records of the Department of Chemical Engineering largely from the period when it was under the leadership of Chairman Joseph C. Elgin, who would later go on to become Dean of the School of Engineering and Applied Science. The records consist primarily of subject files, correspondence, and departmental materials such as faculty minutes and applications for open positions.
    Arranged chronologically.
    - Royalties - Books, 1940-1941; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Departmental Matters - Condit, 1941; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Fellowships and Assistantships, Appointees, 1941-1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Fellowships and Assistantships, 1940-1941; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Fellowships - Other Institutions, 1940-1941; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Geological Engineering Program, 1940; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Interviews and Employment, 1940-1941; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Letters of Recommendation, 1941; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Organic Technology, 1941; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Sigma Xi, 1941-1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Summer Employment, 1941; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Trinity Church School, 1941; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Alumni Fund, 1941; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - Letters of Recommendation, 1940; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Fellowship Applications, 1939-1940; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Teaching Position Applications, 1934-1937; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - General Correspondence, 1940; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - Department Report, 1937-1938; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - Professional License, 1938; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - Monsanto Fellowship, 1937-1938; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 20)
    - Projects Committee, 1938; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 21)
    - Student Chapter Affairs, 1940; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 22)
    - Instructorship Applications and Correspondence, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence for Record, 1936; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 24)
    - Student Chapter Speakers and Affairs, 1938; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 25)
    - Fellowships, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 26)
    - Fellowship Inquiries and Applications, 1937; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 27)
    - General Correspondence, 1940-1941; 2 folders (Box 128, Folder 28 to 29)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1942-1943; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 30)
    - Fellowship and Graduate Work Inquiries, 1939-1940; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 31)
    - Fellowship Applications, 1939; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 32)
    - Fellowship Inquiries and Applications, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 33)
    - Fellowship Inquiries and Letters, 1940; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 34)
    - Graduate Work and Fellowship Inquiries, 1940-1941; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 35)
    - Personnel Inquiries and Student Employment, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 36)
    - Personnel Interviews, 1937; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 37)
    - Personnel and Job Interviews, 1939-1940; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 38)
    - American Institute of Chemical Engineers, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 39)
    - American Institute of Chemical Engineers Projects Committee, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 40)
    - A - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 41)
    - B - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 42)
    - Changes in Schedules and Exams, 1941-1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 43)
    - Chemical Engineer's Handbook, J. H. Perry, 1941-1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 44)
    - Condit, Kenneth H, 1941-1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 45)
    - Course Grades, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 46)
    - C - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 47)
    - Departmental Report, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 48)
    - D - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 49)
    - E - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 50)
    - F - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 51)
    - G - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 52)
    - H - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 53)
    - Industrial Interviews, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 54)
    - I - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 55)
    - J - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 56)
    - K - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 57)
    - L - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 58)
    - M - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 59)
    - N - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 60)
    - O - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 61)
    - Professorships Elsewhere, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 62)
    - P - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 63)
    - Reading Period, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 64)
    - Recommendation Letters, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 65)
    - Sigma Xi, 1941-1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 66)
    - Summer E. D. T. Course, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 67)
    - Summer Session, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 68)
    - S. Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 69)
    - Tyler, Stephen L, 1941-1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 70)
    - T - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 71)
    - V - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 72)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 73)
    - X - Y - Z - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 74)
    - Shaw, Dexter, 1941-1942; 2 folders (Box 128, Folder 75 to 76)
    - Jute Application, 1941; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 77)
    - Card File, undated; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 78)
    - Advisory Committee on Educational Policy for the School of Engineering, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Chemical Engineering Faculty Minutes, 1957-1959; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Chemical Engineering Faculty Minutes, 1945-1957; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Engineering School Executive Committee Minutes1951-1959, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1953 April - December, 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1953 January - March, 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Engineering School Faculty Minutes, 1944-1958; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Advisory Council, 1958-1959; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Advisory Council, 1957-1958; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Advisory Council, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Graduate Program, 1957-1962; 13 folders
      - Inquiries, 1958; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 4)
      - Inquiries, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 5)
      - Inquiries, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 6)
      - Admission Lists, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 7)
      - Declinations, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 8)
      - Admissions, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 9)
      - Unqualified or Declinations, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 10)
      - Admissions, 1958-1959; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 11)
      - Unsuccessful Candidates, 1958-1959; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 12)
      - Admissions, 1957-1958; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 13)
      - Unsuccessful Candidates, 1957-1958; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 14)
      - Declinations, 1957-1958; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 15)
      - Inquiries, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Petty Cash, 1957-1960; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Interviews and Jobs, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 18)
    - Teaching Positions - Inquiries, 1950-1960; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - Teaching Positions Available, 1956-1959; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence and Visits to Department, 1952-1957; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 21)
    - Monsanto Chemical, 1942-1951; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Chemical Engineering Advisory Council, 1942-1949; 4 folders
      - 1949, 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 2)
      - 1948, 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 3)
      - 1947, 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 4)
      - 1942-1946, 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Graduate Program, 1946-1953; 12 folders
      - Admissions, 1948; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 6)
      - Fellowships Elsewhere, 1950-1952; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 7)
      - Admissions and Fellowships, 1946-1953; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 8)
      - Application Summaries, 1947; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 9)
      - Inquiries, 1947-1949; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 10)
      - Recommendations, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 11)
      - Fellowships Schedule, 1948; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 12)
      - Graduate Catalogue, 1946-1947; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 13)
      - Graduate Student Orientation, 1949-1950; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 14)
      - Engineering 445-446 Reports, 1951-1952; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 15)
      - Unsuccessful Applications, 1946-1947; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 16)
      - Fellowships Elsewhere, 1947-1949; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - Stokes Fellowship - Congleton, 1941-1944; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 18)
    - Requests for Positions Here, 1949-1951; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 19)
    - Paul, George T, 1942-1952; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 20)
    - Teaching Positions Available, 1949-1952; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 21)
    - Jobs Available, 1947-1950; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 22)
    - Draft Deferment, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Engineering Minutes, 1940-1948; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 24)
    - Dean Condit, 1949-1950; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 25)
    - Engineering School - General, 1945-1951; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 26)
    - World War II Casualties, 1942; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Teaching Assistantships, 1949; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Engineering Schedule Committee, 1942-1949; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Servicemen - Failure Letters, 1946; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee of the Central Advisory Board for Returning Servicemen, 1944-1946; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Demobilization Committee, 1944; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Returning Servicemen, 1945 November-1946 September; 3 folders
      - 1945 November, 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 7)
      - 1946 March, 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 8)
      - 1946 July-September, 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Engineering School Faculty Minutes, 1941-1946; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Engineering General, 1942-1946; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Draft and Graduate Deferment - World War II, 1943; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Chemical Engineering Building Revisions, 1946-1949; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - Examinations and Standing Committee, 1944-1948; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - University, 1935-1936; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 15)
    - National Defense Research Committee, 1943; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 16)
    - Synthetic Rubber Technology Course Lists, 1945; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1943; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 18)
    - Elgin, J. C. - Patent Application, 1944; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 19)
    - National Defense Research Committee, 1940-1943; 3 folders
      - Correspondence, 1940-1941; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 20)
      - Confidential Correspondence, 1941; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 21)
      - Final Report, 1941-1943; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 22)
    - Office of Scientific Research and Development, 1942-1944; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 23)
    - Reprints, 1941-1941; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 24)
    - Third Century Fund, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Departmental, 1944-1951; 6 folders
      - 1951, 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - 1950, 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 3)
      - 1949, 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 4)
      - 1946-1948, 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 5)
      - 1944-1945, 1 folder (Box 133, Folder F .6)
      - 1946-1950, 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Enrollments, Etc, 1929-1935; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Scott, R. F, 1947; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Dictating Equipment Information, 1948; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Equipment Needs, 1945-1950; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Plans, Etc., New Operations Lab, 1950-1952; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Departmental Accounts, 1946-1951; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - President's Report, 1948-1951; 3 folders
      - 1948-1949, 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 14)
      - 1950, 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 15)
      - 1951, 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 16)
    - Teaching Positions Available, 1943-1948; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 17)
    - Assistant Professorships, 1948; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 18)
    - University Council on Athletics, 1947-1950; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 19)
    - Committee on Student Relations, 1952; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 20)
    - Faculty Committee on Athletic Eligibility, 1946-1950; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 21)
    - Army Specialized Training Program in Chemistry, 1943, dates not examined; 1Volume (Box 133, Folder 26)
    - Engineering, Science, and Management War Training, dates not examined; 3 folders
      - 1941-1942, undated; 1 Volume (Box 133, Folder 23)
      - 1943, undated; 1 Volume (Box 133, Folder 24)
      - 1944-1945, undated; 1 Volume (Box 133, Folder 25)
  - Subseries 3B: Department of Chemical Engineering, 1897-1999; 7.5 linear feet 6 boxes
    - 1912 November-1915 June, 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - 1915 September-1917 March, 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - 1917 April-1918 November, 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - 1918 December-1920 June, 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - 1920 September-1921 June, 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - 1921-1923, 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - 1922 October-1929 April, 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Papers of Professor Frank Henry Constant, 1897-1923; 3 boxes
      - Application - Entrance, 1917-1918; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - Application - Military, 1917-1918; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - Application for Position, 1917; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 3)
      - Application - Teacher, 1918; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - Army, 1917; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 5)
      - Beggs, 1918; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 6)
      - Bills, 1918; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 7)
      - General Black, 1918; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 8)
      - Brown, G. S, 1918; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 9)
      - Brown University, 1918; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 10)
      - Book Review, undated; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 11)
      - Bureau of Municipal Information, 1917; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 12)
      - Civil Engineering, 1917-1918; 4 folders
        - Department, 1917-1918; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 13)
        - Laboratory, 1918; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 14)
        - Schedule, 1917; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 15)
        - Students, undated; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 16)
      - Civil Service, undated; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 17)
      - Class of, 1921; 1918; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 18)
      - Class of, 1918; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 19)
      - Class of, 1917; 1917-1918; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 20)
      - Class of, 1916; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 21)
      - Class of, 1911; 1917; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 22)
      - Close, G. D, 1918; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 23)
      - Colleges, 1917-1918; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 24)